day thirty four
and my dark circles are growing
damn
look at this bro
celebrate the day with one thousand two hundred and fifty-six
and fifteen
-189 on this whiteboard here
now need to fill the tank and spend a silver dough
I ate twenty-seven ninety in the parking lot
the mall was seventeen hundred and ninety-five reais
and seventy three in my box
а
you fish bigger fish have to invest in the bait
is on
his tick requires tension
understanding bagged
you have to realize that you handle
that solution she needs
turned on
brother consulting
if you can understand storytelling
i can close for you 1 plan of god sitting
analyze your case
study
write down do all this
1,500reais package
interested
clear hand
it's time
I'm already imagining here
34 days you have less money
you don't have to be in a hurry
you need to have strategy
turned on
what a cool brother
it's right
beating straight count
thanks again
we are with my brother
look congratulations good
Dona Couto
truffle us
I'm here
with truffle replacement
my god it's heavy
passive income
today 366
truffle investment earns me 1.110reais
I am at 11 commercial points
so it has 1 quick turn 1 week
4 places I've been trading
Mars consulting is open for 1,500reals
и
haha